melissa = User.create(username: "melissafunk", password: "hello")

q1 = Question.create(prompt: "Who speaks the first line of the series?", option1: "Lorelai Gilmore", option2: "Rory Gilmore", option3: "Luke Danes", option4: "Emily Gilmore", answer: "Lorelai Gilmore")
q2 = Question.create(prompt: "What is the name of Babette's cat that dies in Season 1?", option1: "Sugar", option2: "Cinnamon", option3: "Salty", option4: "Sammy", answer: "Cinnamon")
q3 = Question.create(prompt: "What does Rory shoplift after her first kiss with Dean?", option1: "Cornstarch", option2: "Flour", option3: "Sugar", option4: "Baking Powder", answer: "Cornstarch")
q4 = Question.create(prompt: "Who was Richard engaged to before Emily?", option1: "Bitty Charleston", option2: "East Side Tilly", option3: "Karen Gleason", option4: "Pennilyn Lott", answer: "Pennilyn Lott")
q5 = Question.create(prompt: "To earn extra credit, Chilton students sang the school song in what language?", option1: "Japanese", option2: "Italian", option3: "German", option4: "Latin", answer: "Latin")
q6 = Question.create(prompt: "What was Luke's nickname in high school?", option1: "Champ", option2: "Butch", option3: "Dirch", option4: "Larry", answer: "Butch")
q7 = Question.create(prompt: "Which day of the year is Luke's 'dark day'?", option1: "December 3rd", option2: "October 10th", option3: "November 30th", option4: "January 5th", answer: "November 30th")
q8 = Question.create(prompt: "What item does Lorelai constantly have to borrow?", option1: "Stapler", option2: "Scissor", option3: "Paper", option4: "Pen", answer: "Pen")
q9 = Question.create(prompt: "Who took over Tristan's role in Romeo and Juliet?", option1: "Paris", option2: "Mr. Medina", option3: "Dean", option4: "Brad", answer: "Paris")
q10 = Question.create(prompt: "Who is Dean's friend that Lane desperately wanted to go out with?", option1: "Kevin", option2: "Tony", option3: "Tom", option4: "Todd", answer: "Todd")
q11 = Question.create(prompt: "What movie did Dean and Rory watch on their first date?", option1: "Willy Wonka", option2: "Casablanca", option3: "Funny Girl", option4: "Guys and Dolls", answer: "Willy Wonka")
q12 = Question.create(prompt: "Why did Rory end up in jail?", option1: "She sunk a boat", option2: "She got drunk on a boat", option3: "She stole a boat", option4: "She broke a boat", answer: "She stole a boat")
q13 = Question.create(prompt: "What is Kirk's girlfriend's name?", option1: "Lulu", option2: "Linda", option3: "Lucy", option4: "Lindsay", answer: "Lulu")
q14 = Question.create(prompt: "Where is Dean originally from?", option1: "New York", option2: "Chicago", option3: "Denver", option4: "Boston", answer: "Chicago")
q15 = Question.create(prompt: "Who is Jess's father?", option1: "Jimmy", option2: "Joey", option3: "Jeffrey", option4: "Johnny", answer: "Jimmy")
q16 = Question.create(prompt: "What month were Lorelai and Luke going to get married?", option1: "April", option2: "May", option3: "June", option4: "July", answer: "June")
q17 = Question.create(prompt: "Who wins the 24-hour dance marathon?", option1: "Lorelai", option2: "Sooki", option3: "Miss Patty", option4: "Kirk", answer: "Kirk")
q18 = Question.create(prompt: "What is the name of Paris Geller's life coach?", option1: "Terrance", option2: "Thomas", option3: "Tucker", option4: "Trent", answer: "Terrance")
q19 = Question.create(prompt: "When Taylor suggests reviving Stars Hollow's original street names, the new Dragonfly Inn address will be on which street?", option1: "Buckets of Blood Alley", option2: "Warts and Boils Alley", option3: "Sores and Boils Alley", option4: "Blister and Boils Alley", answer: "Sores and Boils Alley")
q20 = Question.create(prompt: "Where do Paris and Rory spend spring break in season 4?", option1: "California", option2: "Florida", option3: "Hawaii", option4: "New Orleans", answer: "Florida")
q21 = Question.create(prompt: "What song kicks off the season 1 pilot at the start of the episode?", option1: "Then She Appeared by XTC", option2: "There She Goes by The La's", option3: "I Try by Macy Gray", option4: "So Says I by The Shins", answer: "There She Goes by The La's")
q22 = Question.create(prompt: "What was the name of the man Lorelai dated who prompted her to try and learn how to fish?", option1: "Andrew", option2: "Aiden", option3: "Adam", option4: "Alex", answer: "Alex")
q23 = Question.create(prompt: "What two fruits did Jackson cross-pollinate?", option1: "Raspberry and Kumquat", option2: "Strawberry and Kumquat", option3: "Boysenberry and Kumquat", option4: "Blackberry and Kumquat", answer: "Raspberry and Kumquat")
q24 = Question.create(prompt: "What was the name of the neighbor who took over Beenie Morrison's old place?", option1: "David", option2: "Damian", option3: "Derek", option4: "Dwight", answer: "Dwight")
q25 = Question.create(prompt: "What was the name of Dean's friend who joined the navy?", option1: "Kevin", option2: "Kyle", option3: "Cole", option4: "Clay", answer: "Kyle")
q26 = Question.create(prompt: "What was the name of the short-lived diner worker who had once dissected a frog, did not wash his hands, and then ate a sandwich?", option1: "Brandon", option2: "Bryan", option3: "Brady", option4: "Brennon", answer: "Brennon")
q27 = Question.create(prompt: "Who did not guest star or appear on the show?", option1: "Nick Offerman", option2: "Krysten Ritter", option3: "Christian Slater", option4: "Melora Hardin", answer: "Christian Slater")
q28 = Question.create(prompt: "Fill in the blank from this quote from Sherry: 'Maureen told me that __________ said that if you squat, it makes the baby come out faster'.", option1: "Howard Stern", option2: "Sam Kinison", option3: "Dave Attell", option4: "Joan Rivers", answer: "Howard Stern")
q29 = Question.create(prompt: "Finish this quote from Lorelai: 'I heard he controls the weather and wrote the screenplay for ________!'", option1: "Striptease", option2: "Battlefield Earth", option3: "Gigli", option4: "Glitter", answer: "Glitter")
q30 = Question.create(prompt: "What is Christopher's favorite band?", option1: "Rancid", option2: "Metallica", option3: "The OffSpring", option4: "XTC", answer: "The OffSpring")
q31 = Question.create(prompt: "What was the name of Luke's first wife?", option1: "Nicole", option2: "Danielle", option3: "Ashley", option4: "Lauren", answer: "Nicole")
q32 = Question.create(prompt: "What's the name of the man who attempts to make the world's largest pizza?", option1: "Tony", option2: "Pete", option3: "Pat", option4: "Stan", answer: "Pete")
q33 = Question.create(prompt: "What is Christopher's mom's name?", option1: "Patricia", option2: "Francine", option3: "Candice", option4: "Evelyne", answer: "Francine")
q34 = Question.create(prompt: "On Sookie & Jackson's first date, what type of seafood does Sookie ask the waiter about?", option1: "Clams", option2: "Scallops", option3: "Oysters", option4: "Mussels", answer: "Mussels")
q35 = Question.create(prompt: "What kind of dessert does Rory make for Dean after watching The Donna Reed Show?", option1: "Gelatin Cake", option2: "Lime Jello with Cool Whip", option3: "Peach Cobbler", option4: "Chocolate Pudding", answer: "Lime Jello with Cool Whip")
q36 = Question.create(prompt: "What is the name of the reverend who lives in Stars Hollow?", option1: "Archie Skinner", option2: "Arthur Harlow", option3: "Harry Walker", option4: "Nathaniel Wright", answer: "Archie Skinner")
q37 = Question.create(prompt: "What is the name of Rory & Paris' roomate at Yale who was athletic?", option1: "Janna", option2: "Janet", option3: "Lana", option4: "Tana", answer: "Janet")
q38 = Question.create(prompt: "When Lane says, 'It's like watching the Williams' Sisters', who is she referring to?", option1: "Rory & Lorelai", option2: "Emily & Mrs. Kim", option3: "Paris & Lorelai", option4: "Mrs. Kim & Mrs. Kim's mom", answer: "Emily & Mrs. Kim")
q39 = Question.create(prompt: "Which of these are things that Paul Anka is NOT afraid of?", option1: "green grapes", option2: "people wearing watches", option3: "peas", option4: "CDs", answer: "green grapes")
q40 = Question.create(prompt: "Which actor is Lorelai referencing when she says to her contractors who are renovating her home, 'I will find you, no matter how long, no matter how far! I will find you!'?", option1: "Jack Nicholson", option2: "Daniel Day Lewis ", option3: "Robert De Niro", option4: "Marlon Brando", answer: "Daniel Day Lewis ")
q41 = Question.create(prompt: "Which song does Hep Alien NOT cover?", option1: "Time Bomb", option2: "London Calling", option3: "Hanging on the Telephone", option4: "Should I Stay or Should I Go", answer: "Should I Stay or Should I Go")
q42 = Question.create(prompt: "What item of clothing does Emily find, which Richard wears for his acapella singing group?", option1: "Red Bow Tie", option2: "Rainbow Suspenders", option3: "Glittery Vest", option4: "Fedora Hat", answer: "Glittery Vest")
q43 = Question.create(prompt: "What movie did Lane and Zack watch on their first date?", option1: "Stop Making Sense", option2: "True Stories", option3: "Gimme Shelter", option4: "The Last Waltz", answer: "Stop Making Sense")
q44 = Question.create(prompt: "What was NOT on the original to-do list for Rory's impending departure to Yale?", option1: "Presents for Friends", option2: "Candy Fest at Taylor's Soda Shoppe", option3: "Mani Pedis", option4: "Watch Godfather Movies", answer: "Candy Fest at Taylor's Soda Shoppe")
q45 = Question.create(prompt: "When Lane dyes her hair with bleach, what does Rory suggest she drink to help ease the pain?", option1: "7up", option2: "Ginger Ale", option3: "Salad Water", option4: "Pepsi", answer: "7up")
q46 = Question.create(prompt: "Logan's colleague, Bobby, gets up and says what during a business meeting?", option1: "Nice Try Fellas", option2: "Decent Attempt Guys", option3: "Meetings Over Boys", option4: "Can You Handle It", answer: "Meetings Over Boys")
q47 = Question.create(prompt: "What do the Yale Daily News colleauges NOT give Rory on her last day as editor-in-chief?", option1: "Giant Pencil", option2: "Front Page of Last Edition as Editor", option3: "Champagne Toast", option4: "Typewriter", answer: "Typewriter")
q48 = Question.create(prompt: "What is the Stars Hollow knit-a-thon fundraiser for?", option1: "To fix a town bridge", option2: "To fix up the town gazebo", option3: "To add a traffic light", option4: "To donate to the church", answer: "To fix a town bridge")
q49 = Question.create(prompt: "When Paris says, 'Whatever strawhead actor isn't?', which actor is she responding about?", option1: "James Van Der Beek", option2: "Brad Pitt", option3: "Ryan Reynolds", option4: "Ryan Phillippe", answer: "Ryan Phillippe")
q50 = Question.create(prompt: "What does Emily do that prompts Lorelai to say, 'That'll do pig'?", option1: "Emily does a spot-on impression of Richard", option2: "Emily eats her meal slowly", option3: "Emily eviscerates Logan's mom", option4: "Emily has tea with Richard's mother", answer: "Emily eats her meal slowly")

